question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Han Solo's co-pilot and best friend, &quot;Chewbacca&quot;, is an Ewok.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004's 'The Aviator'",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The film '2001: A Space Odyssey' was released on December 31st, 2000.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original script of 'The Matrix', the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Shaquille O'Neal appeared in the 1997 film 'Space Jam'.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Ewan McGregor did not know the name of the second prequel film of Star Wars during and after filming.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, 'Bad Motherf*cker' in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock's film 'Psycho' it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, David Prowse was the actor who physically portrayed Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio's character hunts down the killer of his son.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Brandon Routh plays the titular character in the movie 'John Wick'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "'Foodfight!' earned less than $80,000 at box office.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
